Guide to the New York State College of Home Economics records, 1875-1979
Cornell University, New York State College of Home Economics records,
- Series XI: Photographs
  - Martha Van Rensselaer
    - Outdoor shot of Martha Van Rensselaer (far right) with four other young women, 80 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Martha Van Rensselaer and Flora Rose on the back roof of the old home economics building (now Comstock Hall), 81 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Martha Van Rensselaer and Flora Rose at meeting of League of Women Voters at home of Mrs. Franklin Delano Roosevelt in Hyde Park, New York, 82 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Advisory committee for the Land Grant College Survey. Among those identified in addition to Martha Van Rensselaer are: "Mr. Kline, President Pearson, Dean Mumford, Secretary Jardene, Secretary Work, Governor of Hawaii, Tigert", 1928-05; 83 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Old family portraits, unidentified, and in some cases badly faded and retouched, 84-87 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - At the meeting of the League of Women Voters, Hyde Park, New York, 88 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - N.G. Van Rensselaer at 93 (Martha Van Rensselaer's grandmother). She lived to 102, 89 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Martha Van Rensselaer with other children at about eight years, 90 (Box 55, Folder 5)
      Tintype
    - Martha Van Rensselaer, 1919; 91 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Martha Van Rensselaer, 1923-1924; 92 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Miss Van Rensselaer at her desk. It's good of her but does not show the office to advantage, ca. 1915; 93 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Martha Van Rensselaer at Camp Island, a 30+ acre island in Long Lake she loved so much, 94 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Undated photographs of Martha Van Rensselaer, 95-111 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Copy of portrait painting of Martha Van Rensselaer. Photograph made from glass negative, 112 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Portrait of Martha Van Rensselaer, 1927 (Box 100)
    - Photograph of Martha Van Rensselaer, 1928 (Box 100)
    - Martha Van Rensselaer and Flora Rose riding horses in the Grand Canyon, 1915 (Box 49)
    - Photograph of Native American Festival (panorama) taken by Hugh Troy, 1924 (Box 64)
  - Slides
    - Africa - Nairobi - Workshops led by Dean Canoyer and Sponsored by the U.S. State Department and the International Cooperation Administration, 1961 (Box 68)
    - Paris and Switzerland, 1963 (Box 68)
    - Denmark (Box 68)
    - Copenhagen (Box 68)
    - Japan, Greece, Bangkok, Asia and Greece, 1967 (Box 68)
    - Philippines, 1967 (Box 68)
    - Japan, 1967 (Box 68)
    - Eight slides of Colorado (Box 68)
    - Five slides of Dean Canoyer, 1963 (Box 68)
    - Home Economics, 1960 (Box 68)
    - Slides of MVR Hall, 1962 (Box 68)
    - Slides of Dr. Dora Erway's paintings - she was an emeritus faculty member of the College of Home Economics from 1921-1956 (Box 68)
    - Following slides of College of Home Economics and faculty members:, 1964 (Box 68)
    - M. Bennett in Kitchen (Box 68)
    - Workers in the Kitchen (Box 68)
    - Lippala Teaching in Amphitheater (Box 68)
    - Cafeteria line (Box 68)
    - Chemistry Lab (Box 68)
    - Department Meeting (Box 68)
    - Nursery School Interior (Box 68)
    - Dr. Mondy Demonstrating in Food Lab (Box 68)
    - Food Lab (Box 68)
    - Miss Helen Canoyer (Box 68)
    - Kathryn Walker in Office (Box 68)
    - Fred Kunz and Student (Box 68)
    - Feldman Research (Box 68)
    - Nancy Conklyn in Office (Box 68)
    - Year 1964
      - Dean Canoyer (Box 68)
      - Dean Canoyer's two secretaries (Box 68)
      - Jan Warren teaching in room 117 (Box 68)
      - Housing Design Department - Art Lab (slide used to show in Ghana) (Box 68)
      - Class in Amphitheater (Box 68)
      - Several slides of the Food Lab (Box 68)
      - Textiles and Clothing Department meeting (Box 68)
      - Textiles and Clothing (Box 68)
      - Textiles and Clothing- Humphrey Lab (Box 68)
      - Child Development and Family Relations Department Meeting (Box 68)
    - 1965, Some of these slides were used for Parents Weekend and for Japanese Tour Group
      - Commencement Parade (Box 68)
      - Seminar (Box 68)
      - Classroom Nursery School Outdoors (Box 68)
      - Students using Microscopes (Box 68)
      - Olin Files (Box 68)
      - Fall in Ithaca (Box 68)
      - MVR (Box 68)
      - Stacks in Library (Box 68)
      - The End (Box 68)
      - HD Modular Construction (Box 68)
      - Household Economics and Management Eco Conference (Box 68)
      - Household Economics and Management Work Simplification (Box 68)
      - Home Economics Education - Student Teacher (Box 68)
      - Child Development and Family Relations (Box 68)
      - Home Economics Education (Box 68)
      - Child Development and Family Relations Nursery School (Box 68)
      - Textiles and Clothing Seminar (Box 68)
      - Institutional Management (Box 68)
      - HD (Box 68)
      - Textiles and Clothing -Textiles Lab (Box 68)
  - Homemaking house, various student activities (Box 101)
  - Photographs
    - Alumni Association
      - Ithacans get together: Miss Anna Hunn (L: class of 1912) and Mrs.A.M.Goodman (R: class of 1912) tell Mrs. Michael Brown (class of 1952) about the early days at Cornell (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - Flora Rose and (Dean) Helen Canoyer talk together (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - Dean Canoyer and Flora Rose at Home Economics Breakfast, 1954 (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - Flora Rose, Dean Canoyer, and Dorothy DeLany at Cornell Dinner in San Francisco, 1954 (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - Present and past participants of the HE Alumnae Assoc, get together a coffee hour. Present: Dorothy DeLany (1923), Alberta Dent Shackelton (1920), Jeannette Gardiner Powell (1926), Dorothy Fessenden Sayles (1925), current President Helen Bull Vandervort (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - The Alumnae Institute Banquet, Present at table: Professor Emerita Beulah Blackmore, Professor Faith Fenton (Food and Nutrition),Professor Emeritus Ruth Scott, Anna Hunn (1912), Rose Brodbeck Padgham (1940) (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - Professor Elizabeth Conrad and Claribel Nye discuss liquid detergent while Doris Wadsworth Toole (1923) examines a box of detergents (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - Helen Vandervort and Flora Rose after Miss Rose has been presented a surprise birthday cake at the Alumnae Institute Banquet, 1954 (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - Helen Vandervort applauds as waitress presents Flora Rose with a surprise birthday cake, 1954 (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - Helen Vandervort and Flora Rose chat at the banquet, 1954 (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - Alberta Shackelton talks with Dean Helen Canoyer at the banquet (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - Flora Rose (former director of the College) and Clarabel Nye examine portrait of Miss Rose in the College of Home Economics Lounge (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - Flora Rose and Clarabel Nye sitting together (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Apartment 'A'
      - Two students get a frozen dinner from the freezer (Box 77, Folder 2)
      - Two students heat the frozen dinner in Apartment A (Box 77, Folder 2)
      - Apartment A. (a homemaking apartment)is decorated with curtains (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Apartment Baby
      - A woman feeds the practice baby in a highchair, 1950 (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - Joseph, the practice baby, gets his diaper changed by two students in the college, 1946 (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - The practice baby gets weighed by two students, 1944 (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - Two students play with the practice baby, 1954 (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - A students gets practical experience with the practice baby in his stroller, 1945 (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - A group of graduate students and the practice baby, 1944 (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - A baby picture a few days old (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - A baby picture (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - A baby picture a wonderful smile (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - Two students weigh a baby (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - A picture taken in Apartment A includes Dorothy Dye Spencer, and other men and women eating dinner, 1950-1959 (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - Three women play with a baby, 1949 (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - The cook and the mother for the week prepare a baby cereal that can also be eaten by adults (practice in Apartment A), 1946 (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - The mother for the week serves 'the family' in the homemaking apartment, 1946 (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - Baby Bonnie dandled in the lap of a student. another student looks on (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - Two students play with the practice baby in the homemaking apartments of the College of Home Economics (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - Testing with an eight month old baby in the homemaking apartment, 1950 (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - Four students speak into a microphone and play with the baby (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - A student plays with the baby, 1946 (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - A student feeds the baby its bottle, 1946 (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - Another student feeds the baby (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - Men and Women watch as one woman plays with a baby in his high chair (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Campus Scenes
      - Exterior Pictures
        - Three young women talking outside of Martha Van Rensselaer Hall (Box 77, Folder 4)
        - Two women coming out of MVR the Extension building, 1951 (Box 77, Folder 4)
        - Three women sit and talk outside of MVR in the sunshine, 1951 (Box 77, Folder 4)
        - Summer Session, three women talking outside, 1951 (Box 77, Folder 4)
        - Three women talking in the grass behind MVR Summer Session, 1951 (Box 77, Folder 4)
        - MVR Hall, 1933 (Box 77, Folder 4)
        - A woman walking through a snowy path to MVR's central entrance (Box 77, Folder 4)
        - Two women sit at the foot of the statue of Ezra Cornell, late 1940s (Box 77, Folder 4)
        - Two women study outside the 'New Mann Library", 1951 (Box 77, Folder 4)
        - "Jane and Johnny Parsons"...a woman walking on a dock by a lake, outside a lovely home setting (Box 77, Folder 4)
        - "Shirley and her sorority sisters skip stones and swim at Buttermilk Falls on a sunny afternoon" (Box 77, Folder 4)
        - A scene outside MVR on a sunny day, 1945-1955 (Box 77, Folder 4)
        - Four women laugh and talk by the bridge at Beebe Lake (Box 77, Folder 4)
        - Jean Beiermeister, Shirley, Peggy Kaufman, and Pat Robertson study for finals and take in the sun at Buttermilk Falls (Box 77, Folder 4)
        - A very old picture of the Agriculture Quad, 1900-1920 (Box 77, Folder 4)
      - Martha Van Rensselaer Hall
        - MVR Hall Exterior -three construction photos when MVR was being built, 1932 (Mapcase-folder DD-14)
        - MVR Hall Exterior, 1951 (Box 77, Folder 5)
        - A picture of an amphitheater, now a furnace room, with a woman giving a lecture to many female students (Box 77, Folder 5)
        - MVR Hall, 1951 (Box 77, Folder 5)
        - MVR Hall from the front, 1951 (Box 77, Folder 5)
        - A view of the East end, the new building, 1951 (Box 77, Folder 5)
        - MVR Hall, 1951 (Box 77, Folder 5)
        - MVR Hall, 1951 (Box 77, Folder 5)
        - Looking at Martha Van Rensselaer Hall from the direction of Bailey Hall, 1951 (Box 77, Folder 5)
        - The center entrance to MVR Hall (Box 77, Folder 5)
        - Marilyn Jaffe and Nancy Fraser looking at a flower bed outside of MVR Hall (three pictures) (Box 77, Folder 5)
        - Profesor Julia Adler, 1961 (Box 77, Folder 5)
        - Professor Jean Warren, 1961 (Box 77, Folder 5)
        - Patricia Ey, testing raincoat fabric for water repellent (Box 77, Folder 5)
        - Three scenes at the entrance of Martha Van Rensselaer Hall (Box 77, Folder 5)
        - A view of MVR from the Ag Quad, 1966 (Box 77, Folder 5)
        - A view of MVR Hall from the Ag Quad, 1951 (Box 77, Folder 5)
        - A view of the center entrance to Martha Van Rensselaer Hall, 1951 (Box 77, Folder 5)
        - A view of the back of Martha Van Rensselaer Hall (east side), 1956 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Campus
    - Students getting some sun and swimming by Beebe Lake (three pictures) (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Students talking and studying on Libe Slope (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Old pictures
    - High School Guidance Counselor Conference at Cornell, 1966-10 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Same as above (assortment of unknown people at MVR) (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Same as above (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Emily Hall's Class working with Professor Phillips, 1966-11 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Susan Matson (portrait), Tompkins County Agent, Home Economics Division (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Knowlton introduces Pat Arkinstall, and Arkinstall speaks (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Trainees in Head Start Program working with children (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Dean Canoyer handing out diplomas, 1965-06 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Handing out diplomas in MVR (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - A woman using a sewing machine, 1918 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - A women and men in an old car (they are winding it up) (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - The first extension service car. Clarabel Nye, Martha Van Rensselaer, Natalie Thompson, Ruth Graham, Catherine Mills, Edna Alderman, an( student driver. (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - A woman in an old style kitchen (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - A woman stitching on a machine, 1918 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Women examining exhibits in the home economics car of a "victory train" at Farm and Home week. (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Two women cooking in an old kitchen (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Founders of the New York State Federation of Home Bureau: Florence Freer, Flora Rose, A. Brigden, Mrs. Vincent Riordan, Anne Putnam, Ruby Green Smith, Lillian Backus, Lewis Seymour, Edith Salisbury, Mrs. M. Armstrong, 1919 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Leaders in Farm interests in New York standing before the covered wagon which made the trip from coast to coast in the interests of low taxes and less legislation. HJ Wallace (center), Victor Underwood (extreme left), Dean Mann, McBurritt. (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Country School Exhibit, Landscape Art Department, Farmer's Week, 1920 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Farmstead Exhibit, Landscape Art Dept. Farmer's Week, 1920 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Hats and gingham dresses made by students, Farmer's Week, 1919 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Farmer's Week guests inspect campus at Cornell (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Group Picture of unknown women (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - CANNING/PRESERVES
    - Home economist canning beets (Box 59, Folder 23)
    - Four students learn how to can tomatoes from a professor. (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Three students examine the canned products in their jars, 1950 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Four students learn how canned products should look from a professor (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - CAREERS BOOKLET
    - Graduates of the College of Home Economics-photos of them at work (Box 59, Folder 16-19)
    - Woman operating a chemical machine, 1968 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Students learning about expenses and resources from a professor, 1967 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Two members of the Advisory Council (Cole, Switzer), 1968 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - same as above (different pose) (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Two members of the Advisory Council (Devereux, Crul), 1968 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Chairwoman of the Advisory Council, Dean Hagadone, 1968 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Yearbook picture of a female student (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - A student trimming fat off meat, 1968 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Three students in an office (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Three pictures of a woman displaying different styles of art in books, 1967 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Negatives and photos of a woman as an elementary school teacher, 1967 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - CHILD DEVELOPMENT and FAMILY RELATIONS
  - Professor Harold Feldman
    - A couple sitting together (interview style) with their young baby in a Child Study, 1962 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - A young child (maybe two years old) playing a game. Looks like a test. (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - A researcher testing cognitive development with above child (Julie) - two photos (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Photo labeled "Poverty Course" (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Three women are studying a toy in a playroom. (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - A young girl (age 4) and a young boy (3 or 4) are playing at a table. The girl is using clay, and the boy is watching her. (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Duplicate in folder 9: Assistant Professor Thomas with homemade toys. (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - An outside play center near to the kitchen window at the home of Mr. and Mrs. Post. (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - A class meets at the home of Professor Russell Smart to observe his baby. One person feeds the baby, while the Professor and 6 other women watch. (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - A scene in a playroom. Four babies of different ages are present and being observed. One nurse is there, and six women are taking notes. (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - The Barton family (parents and four children) participate in the family art project. Picture taken in the lab at the College. (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Glenn Olds (Cornell United Religious Work), Robert Polson (head of Rural Sociology), Leonard Buyse (Vice Principal of Ithaca High School), Edward Pope (professor of Child Development and Family Relationships), and Joseph Burroughs (professor of Child Development and Family Relationships) participate in a symposium on juvenile delinquency. (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Three women and two men play with and observe two young babies (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Same as above (different pose) (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - A graduate student watches children in an art class make puppets in a summer session, 1954 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Assistant Professor Ruth Thomas with homemade toys, 1953 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - A picture promoting the good family life. A father, mother, two children (boy and girl), and a dog sit in front of the fireplace, snacking on popcorn, and listening intently to the father, 1951 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Family of Professor Edward Pope - Father, mother and two boys read the Bible and look at the nativity scene, 1952 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Seven children sit around a man who is holding a white bunny rabbit in an outside setting. (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - A setting for a young girl to work in having paper, pencils, and an appropriate work space cuts down on dawdling, 1950 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Opposite setting of above description. This time the girl is on the floor trying to work, 1950 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Varna Reynolds serves coffee to two members of faculty in the department of Child Development and Family Relationships (Dalton and Wylie), and to two delegates to the Family Life Conference, 1952 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Two young women sit with a collection of dolls and toys. (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Three children and a woman wash their hands in sinks which are low to the ground (their level) (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - A man plays the piano, the woman plays the tambourine, and three children play other instruments together in a home setting. (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - A man is being interviewed in an office setting. (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - TOY WORKSHOP
    - A woman and a man working in the Nursery School Toy Lab (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Parents make Christmas toys in the workshop/Lab, 1942 (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Three students learning their way around a toy workshop, 1957 (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Two students making toys at the driving board (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Three students are assisted by Professor Lambert Britain in the toy lab (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Students making toys they designed themselves. (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - A student uses a power saw to construct a toy (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Assistant Professor Ruth Thomas with homemade toys, 1953 (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Same as above (different pose) (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - A teacher and two children playing with paint (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - CORNELL KITCHEN
    - Kitchen Design-steps marked out, 1946 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - 1951 and 1954
    - A sketch of the Cornell Kitchen (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - A boy pours a glass of milk for a small girl holding a doll, in the kitchen. Photo of the view from the Cornell kitchen window. (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Barbara Kenrick, instructor in Housing and Design dept. stirs soup in the revolutionary Cornell kitchen which can be arranged to suit the needs of the user. Kenrick shows how the garbage can is used. (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Kenrick shows the uses of the adjustable pull out trays inside the cabinet doors. (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Kenrick uses the cutting board which is at seated level. There is another cutting board at standing level. (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Kenrick demonstrates other uses of the kitchen in eight separate pictures.. A picture showing the building process of the kitchen. (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - The janitorial and housekeeping staff surprise Ethel Cox on her 70th birthday. A woman and a baby sitting at the kitchen table A woman using the kitchen accessories (two pictures) (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Professor Glenn Beyer (Housing and Design) looks over the final installation of the "revolutionary" Cornell Kitchen (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - China
    - Six pictures showing how to arrange china plates, cups, bowls, etc. in a kitchen cabinet. (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Cabinets
    - Kitchen Storage Design, 1945 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Kitchen Storage Design, 1946 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Kitchen Storage Design, 1947 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Kitchen Storage Design, 1949 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Seven pictures of different assortments and organizations of kitchen cupboards. (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - Two pictures of the under range storage cabinets of the kitchen (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - Four pictures of the kitchen sink cabinets in different formations (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - Three pictures of kitchen, swing cabinets (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Research Equipment
    - Five pictures showing models of cabinets and kitchenware, including their dimensions (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - Beehive and Combination Toolbox set (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Home Canning Machine (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Laundry Room (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Laundry-Washing Machine, 1912 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Pots and Pans (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Woman using an early stove (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Early stove and tea set (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Storage Wall
    - Fourteen pictures showing the storage cabinets, (doors open, closed,shelves filled, empty) (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - Two pictures showing the wall panel for pans, utensils and supplies (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - CORNELL RADIO STATION
  - ET and I Radio
    - The Department of Extension Teaching and Information puts out a radio broadcast daily. Here, a woman sits at the microphone (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - Four women reading information over the radio waves (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - Three women doing layout for a newspaper, 1947 (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - The station is named WHCU. Two women sit at a table by the microphone having a discussion. (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - Nina Kuznick and Catherine Personius talk while on the air about a chemistry/nutrition set up, 1945-09 (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - A man from WJZ radio gives a broadcast (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - COUNSELING
    - An advisor (from the counseling staff) and a student talking in an office (Box 77, Folder 18)
    - Jean Failing and three students looking at a map of Cornell, 1947 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - DEPARTMENTS
  - Administration
    - Conference Room /Jean Failing in Center (two photos) Portrait of Esther Stocks (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - CDFR Human Ecology
    - Family Life Conference: MVR Hall(3 pictures), 1956 (Box 77, Folder 20)
    - A woman and a child are playing with a white mouse (Box 77, Folder 20)
    - A teacher and some children are playing with a hamster (Box 77, Folder 20)
    - A small boy is playing the guitar (Box 77, Folder 20)